<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Furry Games Index</title>
<description>A project to index furry &amp; kemono games. - RSS Feed will push the 50 most recent game entries added to FGI in chronological order.</description>
<link>https://furrygames.top/en</link>
<copyright>FurryGamesIndex project. All rights reserved</copyright>
<ttl>1800</ttl>
<item>
<title>Pokémon Mystery Dungeon: Explorers of Sky</title>
<description><![CDATA[
	<img width='360' height='168' src='../assets/Pokemon_Mystery_Dungeon_Explorers_of_Sky/thumbnail.jpg?hc=uquery&t=1719016768' alt='' loading='lazy'><br><br>
	A Pokémon dungeon crawler/roguelike spinoff in which the player wakes up as human-turned-Pokémon with amnesia. It is an enhanced version of Pokémon Mystery  Dungeon: Explorers of Time and Explorer of Darkness. It is based off the Mystery Dungeon series. The player engages in turn-based combat versus other hostile Pokémon while exploring Mystery Dungeons. They start off with a partner Pokémon that is chosen in the beginning of the game as their teammate, but they can add more members later, with a max of four Pokémon on a team.<br><br><br>
	<a href="https://furrygames.top/en/games/Pokemon_Mystery_Dungeon_Explorers_of_Sky.html">https://furrygames.top/en/games/Pokemon_Mystery_Dungeon_Explorers_of_Sky.html</a>
]]></description>
<link>https://furrygames.top/en/games/Pokemon_Mystery_Dungeon_Explorers_of_Sky.html</link>
<guid>https://furrygamesindex.github.io/en/games/Pokemon_Mystery_Dungeon_Explorers_of_Sky.html</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 00:39:28 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Lintw - Animal Story</title>
<description><![CDATA[
	<img width='360' height='168' src='../assets/lintw/thumbnail.jpg?hc=uquery&t=1718982393' alt='' loading='lazy'><br><br>
	This &#34;school&#34; doesn&#39;t tolerate stupid kids---<br>There is only one fate for the poor students, to be locked in a tentacle room<br>and be punished by a hole in their back, even if they cry...<br><br>The Design Philosophy behind Lintw:<br>In Lintw...<br>No one is born with handicaps or sickness.<br>No one becomes suicidal.<br>No one becomes a killer.<br>No one is obligated to work; there are no food troubles.<br>Children study until they are adults, in the adult world they can play until death.<br><br>In Lintw...<br>There is a mechanism to report bad predispositions and to fix it in the next generation.<br>The population is stable. There is no drag on children&#39;s studies.<br>The quality of education does not vary with the times.<br>Crime does not occur, war does not occur; police and legal systems are unnecessary.<br>The social structure is a mesh, so a central government does not exist.<br>This is a World that can talk like friends with anyone on first meet.<br><br>TODO: Create a page about the philosophy of the world of Lintw<br>This world started without any &#34;script&#34;. <br>Tragedies were repeated that benefited neither the performers nor the audience. <br>Our goal is to write a script for this poor world and transform it into a world that follows the plot.<br><br>©2014 konzaburou all rights reserved.<br><br><br>
	<a href="https://furrygames.top/en/games/lintw.html">https://furrygames.top/en/games/lintw.html</a>
]]></description>
<link>https://furrygames.top/en/games/lintw.html</link>
<guid>https://furrygamesindex.github.io/en/games/lintw.html</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 15:06:33 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Before You Depart</title>
<description><![CDATA[
	<img width='360' height='168' src='../assets/before_u_depart/thumbnail.png?hc=uquery&t=1718375406' alt='' loading='lazy'><br><br>
	Canines are often companions for life. Some can even be companions in death...<br><br>This is a SFW visual novel, but player discretion is advised. Our story deals with heavy topics such as:<br><br>Terminal Illness<br>Mental Health<br>Death &amp; Grief<br><br>This project was made for the May Wolf Visual Novel Game Jam. Please go check out the submission made by the other developers!<br><br>This visual novel is a 100% complete experience. Any updates made in the future will be for bug fixes, quality-of-life improvements, or implementing features we didn&#39;t have time to create.<br><br>Love our story? Check out the Before You Depart, Asset Pack! You can download high quality images and our original soundtrack.<br><br><br>
	<a href="https://furrygames.top/en/games/before_u_depart.html">https://furrygames.top/en/games/before_u_depart.html</a>
]]></description>
<link>https://furrygames.top/en/games/before_u_depart.html</link>
<guid>https://furrygamesindex.github.io/en/games/before_u_depart.html</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 14:30:06 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Nine Sols</title>
<description><![CDATA[
	<img width='360' height='168' src='../assets/Nine_Sols/thumbnail.png?hc=uquery&t=1717681693' alt='' loading='lazy'><br><br>
	Nine Sols is a lore rich, hand-drawn 2D action-platformer featuring Sekiro-inspired deflection focused combat. Embark on a journey of Asian fantasy, explore the land once home to an ancient alien race, and follow a vengeful hero’s quest to slay the 9 Sols, formidable rulers of this forsaken realm.<br>Story<br>In New Kunlun, hero Yi has awakened the 9 rulers of this forsaken realm. To defeat the 9 Sols in the deserted city.  <br>“Becomes one with the way of Tao…”  <br>New Kunlun, the Solarian’s last sanctuary, has remained quiet for centuries. Inside this vast realm, the ancient gods left mortals with a promised land that is forever protected by the sacred rituals, yet the truth of this world remains unknown to most. Everything changes when Yi, a long forgotten hero from the past, is awoken by a human child.  <br>Follow Yi on his vengeful quest against the 9 Sols, formidable rulers of this forsaken realm, and obliterate any obstacles blocking your way in Sekiro-lite style combat. Explore in unique “Taopunk” setting that blends cyberpunk elements with Taoism and far eastern mythology. Unravel the mysteries of an ancient alien race and learn about the fate of mankind.  <br><br>Features<br>2D Sekiro-lite Combat: Slash, deflect, charge into enemies and blow them up with the Taoist talisman! Each fight combines fast, brutal action sequences with classic platforming mechanics.  <br> <br> <br>Intriguing Boss Fight: Ready yourself to fight the vicious ancient guardians and gruesome creatures. Be patient and utilize every move in your arsenal, mix up with Yi’s godly bow to defeat these larger than life figures.  <br> <br>Taopunk Setting: When cyberpunk clashes with Taoism, melding sci-fi elements with eastern mythology/fantasy, the experimental genre of Taopunk was born.  <br>Exploration: Traverse in the interconnected regions of New Kunlun. Discover secrets, piece together the story behind Yi’s revenge.  <br> <br>Aids from inhabitants: Meet interesting NPCs of this world and interact with them to receive upgrades, gain new abilities, and discover useful technology.  <br>Hand-drawn Environments/Animations and Manga: Nine Sols is filled with meticulous hand-crafted, anime style landscapes, sprite based hand-drawn animations, blending with Japanese manga inspired cutscenes.  <br><br>Red Candle Games<br>From the creators of award-winning psychological horror games Detention and Devotion, comes Red Candle Game’s latest title Nine Sols. The studio aims to deliver a stylized action platformer that’s cohesive and complementary to its lore-rich narrative. It’s an ongoing, most ambitious project from this indie studio.<br><br><br>
	<a href="https://furrygames.top/en/games/Nine_Sols.html">https://furrygames.top/en/games/Nine_Sols.html</a>
]]></description>
<link>https://furrygames.top/en/games/Nine_Sols.html</link>
<guid>https://furrygamesindex.github.io/en/games/Nine_Sols.html</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 13:48:13 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Very Berry Very： Don&#39;t drink that potion</title>
<description><![CDATA[
	<img width='360' height='168' src='../assets/very_berry_very/thumbnail.png?hc=uquery&t=1717518267' alt='' loading='lazy'><br><br>
	Very Berry Very: Don&#39;t drink that potion is a visual novel game set<br><br>in a magical school world with animal(furry) characters as the main characters.<br><br>We aim to create new IP content that anyone can enjoy,<br><br>with a fairytale-like story and humor that is not limited to a specific age group.<br><br>A key feature is that each character has 64 ~ 112 different facial expressions,<br><br>utilizing the various personality factors that animals can have.<br><br>We are going to do crowdfunding on May 10th. Please look forward to.<br><br><br>
	<a href="https://furrygames.top/en/games/very_berry_very.html">https://furrygames.top/en/games/very_berry_very.html</a>
]]></description>
<link>https://furrygames.top/en/games/very_berry_very.html</link>
<guid>https://furrygamesindex.github.io/en/games/very_berry_very.html</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 16:24:27 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Ash Boat</title>
<description><![CDATA[
	<img width='360' height='168' src='../assets/ash/thumbnail.png?hc=uquery&t=1717518254' alt='' loading='lazy'><br><br>
	ALL THE ORIGINAL GAME FILES (GRAPHICS, AUDIOS, TEXT) WILL BE FREELY AVAILABLE UNDER CC BY-SA-NC LICENSE WHEN THIS GAME IS RELEASED. PLEASE CHECK OUT THE ABOUT PAGE IN GAME TO FIND OUT MORE.<br><br>In Ash Boat, you will spectate on the journey a twin from Erkajɤŋ, and uncover the secrets beneath your spectating point of view.<br><br>Some understanding on contemporary literature may be required to read certain sections. Skipping is also plausible and would barely interfere with reading. Note that some sections are of limited legibility and can barely be translated.<br><br>The game text is relatively short, so we&#39;ll have to ask you to slow down, for if you do not, the estimated game time could be less than ten minutes per chapter. We will try our best to make this game a worthy one for you to slow down.<br><br>If you read at a normal speed, the time it takes to finish a chapter in a line is roughly half an hour.<br><br>This game is founded by the director only and accepts no donations. This game is permanently free, so please report below if you paid for a download. It is permitted to distribute the game, but according to our CC license no commercial revenues can be collected.<br><br><br>
	<a href="https://furrygames.top/en/games/ash.html">https://furrygames.top/en/games/ash.html</a>
]]></description>
<link>https://furrygames.top/en/games/ash.html</link>
<guid>https://furrygamesindex.github.io/en/games/ash.html</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 16:24:14 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>獣の神さま</title>
<description><![CDATA[
	<img width='360' height='168' src='../assets/Kemokami/thumbnail.png?hc=uquery&t=1717518237' alt='' loading='lazy'><br><br>
	Beasts of the Five Elements RPG<br>Four beasts are invited to an island.<br>Their mission is to defeat the five demons that avenge the living.<br>The four beasts have the power to do so. Because.<br>Blue Dragon, Suzaku, White Tiger and Genbu.<br>They were the descendants of the five gods who govern the five elements.<br>This is an RPG in which the beasts descended from the five gods are the main characters.<br>The play time is around 4-8 hours and there are two endings.<br>Video submissions and live broadcasts: please feel free to do so!<br><br>7/7 Ver. 1.03 was released.<br>The escape probability has been adjusted.<br>The map, dialogue, etc. have been slightly modified.<br>If you have save data from previous versions, you can transfer to Ver. 1.03.<br>Please transfer all the following files in the folder of the previous version to the Ver. 1.03 folder:<br>Save1-10.rxdata<br>Save1-10_sub.rxdata<br>Master.rxdata<br><br>3/3 Ver. 1.02 was released.<br>The five-element diagram is now displayed during combat after advancing a little further in the adventure.<br>Adventure records can now be viewed.<br><br>2/5 Ver. 1.01 released.<br>Adjustments have been made to the techniques, encounters and movement.<br>The ‘Inheritance’ command has been added to the title from the second week onwards.<br>-Levels and opened treasure chests can be inherited.<br>-Encounter-preventing ornaments will be in your possession from the beginning. <br><br>*This game requires RPG Maker XP RTP (Runtime Package).<br><br><br>
	<a href="https://furrygames.top/en/games/Kemokami.html">https://furrygames.top/en/games/Kemokami.html</a>
]]></description>
<link>https://furrygames.top/en/games/Kemokami.html</link>
<guid>https://furrygamesindex.github.io/en/games/Kemokami.html</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 16:23:57 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>东墙日落奇谭</title>
<description><![CDATA[
	<img width='360' height='168' src='../assets/sunsetmyth/thumbnail.png?hc=uquery&t=1717518219' alt='' loading='lazy'><br><br>
	在《东墙日落奇谭》之中，你将与主角一同经营一家赛博朋克都市中的委托中介处：“日落密室”。<br>在这家开设于咖啡店之后的委托中介处里，您需要用前台的咖啡招待客人，获取信息；为烦恼的委托人解析任务、牵线合适的人手，来完成他们的委托，以此经营这家中介处。以此方式，您可以端坐在委托室之中，了解这个城市背后的秘密、在各方势力之间周旋、揭晓城市之中的阴谋——阻止他们，或者成为其中一员。<br>在那之前，在《试玩章节》中玩家将会与见习佣兵、兼咖啡店员的龙型青年“薛新成”一同，面对一位麻烦的不速之客，完成她的委托，揭晓正章故事中阴谋的前奏。<br>语言支持：简体中文<br>薛新成<br>恩图萨<br>哈瑞<br>“蕊德”<br>关于游戏的后续计划：<br>在试玩章节之后，我们将全速制作《东墙日落奇谭》的本章内容，并尝试展开众筹以及其他语种的本地化工作。<br>在正章之中，我们预计将会进一步丰富游玩内容，并添加更多的可玩系统：包括但不限于“佣兵扭蛋”，“情报系统”等等。同时，正章的文本量、登场角色预计将是《试玩章节》数倍，作为一个新人团队，请给予我们一段时间仔细地打磨，为您呈现一款更好的赛博朋克文字冒险游戏。<br>须知：<br>本游戏《试玩章节》完全免费；<br>本游戏不包含恋爱要素；<br>本游戏仅提供PC端游玩；<br>本游戏《试玩章节》作为独立于正章的“前传故事”，《试玩章节》的主角“薛新成”将在正式章节作为佣兵登场； <br><br><br>
	<a href="https://furrygames.top/en/games/sunsetmyth.html">https://furrygames.top/en/games/sunsetmyth.html</a>
]]></description>
<link>https://furrygames.top/en/games/sunsetmyth.html</link>
<guid>https://furrygamesindex.github.io/en/games/sunsetmyth.html</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 16:23:39 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ミリィ・マリーに安らぎを</title>
<description><![CDATA[
	<img width='360' height='168' src='../assets/Miryimarini_yasuragio/thumbnail.jpg?hc=uquery&t=1712356844' alt='' loading='lazy'><br><br>
	ケモノＲＰＧ<br><br>ピザさんのお話をゲームにしたものです(許可済み)<br><br>プレイ時間 5～6時間程度<br>ＥＤは一つです<br><br>一応順番として<br>『クラフトワーク物語』(ノベルゲーム)<br>『メリー・マリーに幸せを』(ノベルゲーム)<br>『ミリィ・マリーに安らぎを』(ＲＰＧゲーム)<br>『ある魔術師の話』(ミリィ・マリーに安らぎを のおまけゲーム)<br>となっています<br><br>流血やグロなど過激な描写が<br>あるので苦手な方はご注意<br><br><br>
	<a href="https://furrygames.top/en/games/Miryimarini_yasuragio.html">https://furrygames.top/en/games/Miryimarini_yasuragio.html</a>
]]></description>
<link>https://furrygames.top/en/games/Miryimarini_yasuragio.html</link>
<guid>https://furrygamesindex.github.io/en/games/Miryimarini_yasuragio.html</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 22:40:44 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>RainyTower</title>
<description><![CDATA[
	<img width='360' height='168' src='../assets/RainyTower/thumbnail.jpg?hc=uquery&t=1712320765' alt='' loading='lazy'><br><br>
	【作品概要】<br>クリック一つの単純操作。指先一つで宙を飛ぶ！<br>アクションゲームが苦手な方でも、プレイを重ねることで様々な性能を強化していくことができます。<br><br>【ストーリー】<br>未知の惑星へと墜落した宇宙探検隊の一行。<br>彼らは脱出の鍵となる資源を手に入れるため、<br>天を臨む樹の頂を目指すのだった......<br><br>【おまけ】<br>おまけ要素として謎解き要素を用意しております。<br>難易度は高めですが、解けた方にはささやかなお礼をさせていただく予定です。<br>詳細は作品中のイベントをご覧ください。 <br><br><br>
	<a href="https://furrygames.top/en/games/RainyTower.html">https://furrygames.top/en/games/RainyTower.html</a>
]]></description>
<link>https://furrygames.top/en/games/RainyTower.html</link>
<guid>https://furrygamesindex.github.io/en/games/RainyTower.html</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 12:39:25 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>PRINCIPIA</title>
<description><![CDATA[
	<img width='360' height='168' src='../assets/Principia/thumbnail.jpg?hc=uquery&t=1712318268' alt='' loading='lazy'><br><br>
	PRINCIPIA is a Visual novel game featuring anthro races called BeastChild.<br><br>Main characters:<br>Nicolas :  A low-paid kombinat worker. Often smokes  cigars.<br><br>Alfred :  An honored student of Nordburg University .<br><br>Hal:  A pious believer, and sister of the Church .<br><br>Thales:  A youth with intellectual disability, working at the same factory with Nicolas.<br><br>Feature:<br><br>Oddly as a novel with furry characters, the story begins with Nicolas smoking a cigar and complaining about his company. Then Hal notes on his behavior based on her religious belief.<br><br>The subject of this game is Nicolas&#39;s romantic feeling for Hal, and the gap between reality and the ideal world referred to as &#34;The world of harmony&#34; by Hal.<br><br>Staffs:<br><br>The development of PRINCIPIA is based on strong support from my friends, and reassuring help by the contributors. Please take a look at their original contents as well.<br><br>Creator / Developer - Nymn Wales<br>Proofwrite Contributor - Ziwz<br>Plot Adviser - Eucetonia<br>General Adviser - Fizzie,  Ave Capra<br><br><br>
	<a href="https://furrygames.top/en/games/Principia.html">https://furrygames.top/en/games/Principia.html</a>
]]></description>
<link>https://furrygames.top/en/games/Principia.html</link>
<guid>https://furrygamesindex.github.io/en/games/Principia.html</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 11:57:48 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>The Black Chapter</title>
<description><![CDATA[
	<img width='360' height='168' src='../assets/The_Black_Chapter/thumbnail.jpg?hc=uquery&t=1707840556' alt='' loading='lazy'><br><br>
	The story of &#34;The Black Chapter&#34; depicts the main character, Samoan police officer Andy, who, in an accident many years ago, gained access to the Magic Eyes of Flow, which allow him to see through the workings of things. <br>Due to his fear of his new ability and the tragic memories that accompanied it, he has kept his ability sealed since then. <br>In the years that followed Andy became a detective. <br>After ordinary days, because of the transfer of the position, he and his predecessor in the police academy, Gray, jointly investigated a vicious serial murder case - the skinning case. <br>Just when life suddenly changes drastically, Andy&#39;s magic eye gradually awakens. <br>Skin flayers, cult rituals, aliens, spirit-recruiting spells, and a succession of bizarre events force him to face the past that he has already forgotten.<br>About Game<br>The Black Chapter is a typical text adventure game in which the player chooses certain options to advance the plot (i.e., an e-novel).<br>The player will play the game from the point of view of the main character &#34;Andy&#34;.<br>There are three threads in the game, each of which corresponds to one of the three targets.<br>It is expected that the whole 6 chapters, some chapters for the common line, chapter length in more than 1 hour.<br><br><br>
	<a href="https://furrygames.top/en/games/The_Black_Chapter.html">https://furrygames.top/en/games/The_Black_Chapter.html</a>
]]></description>
<link>https://furrygames.top/en/games/The_Black_Chapter.html</link>
<guid>https://furrygamesindex.github.io/en/games/The_Black_Chapter.html</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 16:09:16 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Single Wolfie Goes ONSEN Cruising</title>
<description><![CDATA[
	<img width='360' height='168' src='../assets/Single_Wolfie_Goes_ONSEN_Cruising/thumbnail.jpg?hc=uquery&t=1706026796' alt='' loading='lazy'><br><br>
	東京都・中野区で会社員をしている28歳の狼獣人敷島航識は、会社で発売したロボットのヒットに伴う業績アップで増えた残業や、母親の小言といったストレスを抱えていた。<br>そこへ、後輩の馬獣人である板倉健斗が温泉旅行を提案する。<br>旅行の経験がほぼ皆無だった敷島は、はじめは乗り気ではなかったものの、板倉の熱意に押されて、彼の地元だという群馬県・草津温泉へ、2泊3日の旅に行くことを決心する。<br>初めての温泉旅行、初めて見る風景、初めて食べる食事。<br>さまざまな体験を重ねた、その先で知ることとは────<br><br><br>
	<a href="https://furrygames.top/en/games/Single_Wolfie_Goes_ONSEN_Cruising.html">https://furrygames.top/en/games/Single_Wolfie_Goes_ONSEN_Cruising.html</a>
]]></description>
<link>https://furrygames.top/en/games/Single_Wolfie_Goes_ONSEN_Cruising.html</link>
<guid>https://furrygamesindex.github.io/en/games/Single_Wolfie_Goes_ONSEN_Cruising.html</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 16:26:03 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>MEMORY LEAK</title>
<description><![CDATA[
	<img width='360' height='168' src='../assets/Memory_Leak/thumbnail.jpg?hc=uquery&t=1705767062' alt='' loading='lazy'><br><br>
	WARNING - VIEWER DISCRETION IS ADVISED. THIS STORY FEATURES SEX, VIOLENCE, ABUSE, AND OTHER ADULT CONTENT, AS WELL AS FLASHING LIGHTS AND COLORS. <br>When a two bit hacker gets blackmailed by a computer virus, he is forced to navigate a dangerous path in order to escape its clutches. The player guides him on his adventure, and experiences many &#39;bad ends&#39; along the way...<br>From the Makers of Willy Bear Beach and Notes from the Cape comes MEMORY LEAK , a visual novel game that features branching paths based on skill checks and player choices. The game is played in runs, with the player experiencing many bad ends along the way to victory, all of which are collected in a gallery to be viewed later. <br><br><br>
	<a href="https://furrygames.top/en/games/Memory_Leak.html">https://furrygames.top/en/games/Memory_Leak.html</a>
]]></description>
<link>https://furrygames.top/en/games/Memory_Leak.html</link>
<guid>https://furrygamesindex.github.io/en/games/Memory_Leak.html</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2024 16:11:02 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hollow Knight</title>
<description><![CDATA[
	<img width='360' height='168' src='../assets/Hollow_Knight/thumbnail.png?hc=uquery&t=1693325208' alt='' loading='lazy'><br><br>
	Hollow Knight Expands with Free Content<br> <br>Godmaster - Take your place amongst the Gods. New Characters and Quest. New Boss Fights. Available Now!  <br> <br>Lifeblood - A Kingdom Upgraded! New Boss. Upgraded Bosses. Tweaks and Refinements across the whole game.  <br> <br>The Grimm Troupe - Light the Nightmare Lantern. Summon the Troupe. New Major Quest. New Boss Fights. New Charms. New Enemies. New Friends.  <br> <br>Hidden Dreams - Mighty new foes emerge! New Boss fights. New Upgrades. New Music.<br>Brave the Depths of a Forgotten Kingdom<br>Beneath the fading town of Dirtmouth sleeps an ancient, ruined kingdom. Many are drawn below the surface, searching for riches, or glory, or answers to old secrets.  <br>Hollow Knight is a classically styled 2D action adventure across a vast interconnected world. Explore twisting caverns, ancient cities and deadly wastes; battle tainted creatures and befriend bizarre bugs; and solve ancient mysteries at the kingdom&#39;s heart.  <br><br>Game Features<br><br>Classic side-scrolling action, with all the modern trimmings.  <br>Tightly tuned 2D controls. Dodge, dash and slash your way through even the most deadly adversaries.  <br>Explore a vast interconnected world of forgotten highways, overgrown wilds and ruined cities.  <br>Forge your own path! The world of Hallownest is expansive and open. Choose which paths you take, which enemies you face and find your own way forward.  <br>Evolve with powerful new skills and abilities! Gain spells, strength and speed. Leap to new heights on ethereal wings. Dash forward in a blazing flash. Blast foes with fiery Soul!  <br>Equip Charms! Ancient relics that offer bizarre new powers and abilities. Choose your favourites and make your journey unique!  <br>An enormous cast of cute and creepy characters all brought to life with traditional 2D frame-by-frame animation.  <br>Over 130 enemies! 30 epic bosses! Face ferocious beasts and vanquish ancient knights on your quest through the kingdom. Track down every last twisted foe and add them to your Hunter&#39;s Journal!  <br>Leap into minds with the Dream Nail. Uncover a whole other side to the characters you meet and the enemies you face.  <br>Beautiful painted landscapes, with extravagant parallax, give a unique sense of depth to a side-on world.  <br>Chart your journey with extensive mapping tools. Buy compasses, quills, maps and pins to enhance your understanding of Hollow Knight’s many twisting landscapes.  <br>A haunting, intimate score accompanies the player on their journey, composed by Christopher Larkin. The score echoes the majesty and sadness of a civilisation brought to ruin.  <br>Complete Hollow Knight to unlock Steel Soul Mode, the ultimate challenge!<br><br> <br> <br><br>An Evocative Hand-Crafted World<br>The world of Hollow Knight is brought to life in vivid, moody detail, its caverns alive with bizarre and terrifying creatures, each animated by hand in a traditional 2D style.  <br>Every new area you’ll discover is beautifully unique and strange, teeming with new creatures and characters. Take in the sights and uncover new wonders hidden off of the beaten path.  <br>If you like classic gameplay, cute but creepy characters, epic adventure and beautiful, gothic worlds, then Hollow Knight awaits!  <br> <br> <br><br><br><br>
	<a href="https://furrygames.top/en/games/Hollow_Knight.html">https://furrygames.top/en/games/Hollow_Knight.html</a>
]]></description>
<link>https://furrygames.top/en/games/Hollow_Knight.html</link>
<guid>https://furrygamesindex.github.io/en/games/Hollow_Knight.html</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 16:06:48 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Fall of Porcupine</title>
<description><![CDATA[
	<img width='360' height='168' src='../assets/Fall_of_Porcupine/thumbnail.png?hc=uquery&t=1693179886' alt='' loading='lazy'><br><br>
	About the Game<br> <br>Step into the town of Porcupine and take to the well-loved scrubs of Finley, the newest fledgling doctor to join the ranks of St. Ursula&#39;s hospital. As the seasons in the small-town change and life starts to stir, you&#39;ll soon realize that things aren&#39;t always what they seem: Not everyone is honest with themselves and others, the healthcare industry is not as illustrious as it seemed in medical school, and the work/life balance Finley strives toward might be impossible to achieve.<br>Check out the &#34;Save the World&#34; Edition<br><br>Explore A Beautiful, Diverse World<br>Not only is there a lot to discover in the old hospital, but also in the small town of Porcupine itself. Take the time to meet the villagers and have a beer with them in the local pub, take a trip to the nearby forest, or spend quality time with your friends. <br><br>Hardened Professionals, Sweet Friends<br>The blunt head doctor, the selfless nurse, Finley&#39;s smart friends, and many other residents populate the small town of Porcupine. Engage in funny, profound, and sometimes serious dialogues, in which you&#39;ll be able to choose your answers and influence your relationships.<br>Demonstrate Your Skills and Empathy<br>You don&#39;t even have time to look at the clock because your patients are waiting! Investigate what&#39;s wrong with them through your conversations and treat them in different minigames that challenge you in logic, speed, and skill.<br>Expose Social Injustice And Structural Problems<br> <br>At first glance, the small town is a warm, friendly place where everyone knows and greets each other. But if you live there for any length of time, you&#39;ll suspect that not everyone is as honest as they pretend to be – especially in an unhealthy healthcare-system.   <br>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1710540/Fall_of_Porcupine/<br><br><br>
	<a href="https://furrygames.top/en/games/Fall_of_Porcupine.html">https://furrygames.top/en/games/Fall_of_Porcupine.html</a>
]]></description>
<link>https://furrygames.top/en/games/Fall_of_Porcupine.html</link>
<guid>https://furrygamesindex.github.io/en/games/Fall_of_Porcupine.html</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 23:44:46 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Seeking Light</title>
<description><![CDATA[
	<img width='360' height='168' src='../assets/Seeking_Light/thumbnail.jpg?hc=uquery&t=1687538082' alt='' loading='lazy'><br><br>
	关于这款游戏<br><br>【故事介绍】<br>在和平的葡葡果蜜花园小镇，有一个热心的勇者叫做莱特。他十分喜欢帮助别人，在小镇中过着快乐而自在的生活。直到某天，他的朋友向他道出一个秘密…… <br>“莱特，你一定要……”<br>【玩法介绍】<br>这是一个轻松可爱的剧情向rpg游戏，玩家将与勇者莱特一起在温馨小镇进行愉快生活！  <br><br>你可以与小镇的朋友聊天，探索发现新风景~  <br>帮助居民们完成他们的请求，这是勇者该做的事！  <br>在粉红沙滩钓鱼享受悠闲时光。  <br>烹饪美味食物来送给居民吧。  <br>不过在那之前得先种植作物哦。  <br>对了，再帮镇长做一件新衣服吧！  <br><br>【游戏特色】<br><br>独特的世界观与可爱剧情，内含furry与GB元素，调查发现更多惊喜！<br><br>丰富的小游戏和轻松互动，你可以在这里自由探索，完成各种有趣的任务！<br><br>清新优美的美术风格，游戏中涵盖大量动画，CG与美丽地图场景哦！<br><br><br>【关于游玩】<br>「游戏时长」 <br>2小时<br>「结局数量」 <br>2个结局 <br>解锁特殊回忆剧情且在游戏内达成2个结局将自动进入附赠房间<br>「操作方式」 <br>方向键/鼠标：移动 <br>Shift+方向键： 跑步 <br>空格/鼠标：对话/调查物品（长按空格跳过对话） <br>ESC/鼠标右键：取消/打开菜单<br>【staff】<br>制作人、剧本：lidogegg <br>美术：lidogegg、伊柚 <br>发行：梦结界工作室  <br>特别感谢： <br>音乐感谢Alexander Nakarada，更多引用素材来源详见游戏内ED <br>本游戏使用GameCreator开发<br><br><br>
	<a href="https://furrygames.top/en/games/Seeking_Light.html">https://furrygames.top/en/games/Seeking_Light.html</a>
]]></description>
<link>https://furrygames.top/en/games/Seeking_Light.html</link>
<guid>https://furrygamesindex.github.io/en/games/Seeking_Light.html</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 16:34:42 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Beasts of the Thorns</title>
<description><![CDATA[
	<img width='360' height='168' src='../assets/Beasts_of_the_Thorns/thumbnail.jpg?hc=uquery&t=1687259835' alt='' loading='lazy'><br><br>
	One morning you woke up and found your head went missing. As you&#39;d awakened as a Dullahan, people banished you and your monster friends to The Frontier, a shelter for monsters. You and your friends will give your all to graduate from Frontier College, but an unpredictable storm approaches...<br><br><br>
	<a href="https://furrygames.top/en/games/Beasts_of_the_Thorns.html">https://furrygames.top/en/games/Beasts_of_the_Thorns.html</a>
]]></description>
<link>https://furrygames.top/en/games/Beasts_of_the_Thorns.html</link>
<guid>https://furrygamesindex.github.io/en/games/Beasts_of_the_Thorns.html</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 11:17:15 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Summer Paradise</title>
<description><![CDATA[
	<img width='360' height='168' src='../assets/Summer_Paradise/thumbnail.jpg?hc=uquery&t=1686928391' alt='' loading='lazy'><br><br>
	Edric is an average student in college. He has a normal life, but his friend invites him to the pool, and unexpected things happen along the way...<br><br><br>
	<a href="https://furrygames.top/en/games/Summer_Paradise.html">https://furrygames.top/en/games/Summer_Paradise.html</a>
]]></description>
<link>https://furrygames.top/en/games/Summer_Paradise.html</link>
<guid>https://furrygamesindex.github.io/en/games/Summer_Paradise.html</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 15:13:11 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Mad Rat Dead</title>
<description><![CDATA[
	<img width='360' height='168' src='../assets/Mad_Rat_Dead/thumbnail.png?hc=uquery&t=1685265076' alt='' loading='lazy'><br><br>
	Wreak Havoc to the Rhythm!<br>A rat&#39;s dream has been left unfulfilled before his death...that is, until he gets a second chance at life! Granted the opportunity to redo his last day on Earth, you must utilize the rat&#39;s newfound power to pump his heart in time with the music, lest his own time runs out.<br>You’ve got one day to live and a huge score to settle.<br>Time to put the &#34;beat&#34; in beatdown! Jump, dash, and smash to the rhythm in this music-based action platformer!<br><br><br>
	<a href="https://furrygames.top/en/games/Mad_Rat_Dead.html">https://furrygames.top/en/games/Mad_Rat_Dead.html</a>
]]></description>
<link>https://furrygames.top/en/games/Mad_Rat_Dead.html</link>
<guid>https://furrygamesindex.github.io/en/games/Mad_Rat_Dead.html</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 09:11:16 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Rain World</title>
<description><![CDATA[
	<img width='360' height='168' src='../assets/Rain_World/thumbnail.png?hc=uquery&t=1684582962' alt='' loading='lazy'><br><br>
	 <br>You are a slugcat. The world around you is full of danger, and you must face it – alone. Separated from your family in a devastating flood, you will need to find food and shelter between terrifying torrential downpours which threaten to drown all life. Climb through the ruins of an ancient civilization, evade the jaws of vicious predators, and discover new lands teeming with strange creatures and buried mysteries. Find your family before something makes a meal of you!  <br>Inspired by the simplicity and aesthetics of 16-bit classics, this survival platformer requires clever decision-making, both to catch your own prey and to avoid the jaws of hungry predators. Each ravenous foe in your path will be cunning, vicious and always on the hunt – eager to sink their teeth into you, or even each other. As a small, soft slugcat you must rely on stealth and wit rather than force: learn the ecosystem and turn their strengths to your advantage. Maybe then you can survive… Rain World!<br><br><br>
	<a href="https://furrygames.top/en/games/Rain_World.html">https://furrygames.top/en/games/Rain_World.html</a>
]]></description>
<link>https://furrygames.top/en/games/Rain_World.html</link>
<guid>https://furrygamesindex.github.io/en/games/Rain_World.html</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 11:42:42 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Ori and the Will of the Wisps</title>
<description><![CDATA[
	<img width='360' height='168' src='../assets/Ori_and_the_Will_of_the_Wisps/thumbnail.png?hc=uquery&t=1683985649' alt='' loading='lazy'><br><br>
	The little spirit Ori is no stranger to peril, but when a fateful flight puts the owlet Ku in harm’s way, it will take more than bravery to bring a family back together, heal a broken land, and discover Ori’s true destiny. From the creators of the acclaimed action-platformer Ori and the Blind Forest comes the highly anticipated sequel. Embark on an all-new adventure in a vast world filled with new friends and foes that come to life in stunning, hand-painted artwork. Set to a fully orchestrated original score, Ori and the Will of the Wisps continues the Moon Studios tradition of tightly crafted platforming action and deeply emotional storytelling.<br><br><br>
	<a href="https://furrygames.top/en/games/Ori_and_the_Will_of_the_Wisps.html">https://furrygames.top/en/games/Ori_and_the_Will_of_the_Wisps.html</a>
]]></description>
<link>https://furrygames.top/en/games/Ori_and_the_Will_of_the_Wisps.html</link>
<guid>https://furrygamesindex.github.io/en/games/Ori_and_the_Will_of_the_Wisps.html</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 13 May 2023 13:47:29 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Kibbleton University</title>
<description><![CDATA[
	<img width='360' height='168' src='../assets/Kibbleton_University/thumbnail.jpg?hc=uquery&t=1683109275' alt='' loading='lazy'><br><br>
	<br>Here you are, the new transfer to Kibbleton University (KU), and you just joined a brand-new club. Everything and everyone are new to you, but you might get this strange sense of familiarity about these people. <br><br>Spend some time and build up an education in this new university, meet new students and faculty members on this journey of building your club up! <br><br>KU is a choice-based, comedy, romance, slice of life, NSFW visual novel.  You got to be of the legal age in your country to play this. This game is built to explore ideas that would not be able to exist in the main story of WTDL. <br><br><br>
	<a href="https://furrygames.top/en/games/Kibbleton_University.html">https://furrygames.top/en/games/Kibbleton_University.html</a>
]]></description>
<link>https://furrygames.top/en/games/Kibbleton_University.html</link>
<guid>https://furrygamesindex.github.io/en/games/Kibbleton_University.html</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 10:21:15 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Ori and the Blind Forest</title>
<description><![CDATA[
	<img width='360' height='168' src='../assets/Ori_and_the_Blind_Forest/thumbnail.png?hc=uquery&t=1682141634' alt='' loading='lazy'><br><br>
	The forest of Nibel is dying. After a powerful storm sets a series of devastating events in motion, an unlikely hero must journey to find his courage and confront a dark nemesis to save his home. “Ori and the Blind Forest” tells the tale of a young orphan destined for heroics, through a visually stunning action-platformer crafted by Moon Studios for PC. Featuring hand-painted artwork, meticulously animated character performance, and a fully orchestrated score, “Ori and the Blind Forest” explores a deeply emotional story about love and sacrifice, and the hope that exists in us all.<br><br><br>
	<a href="https://furrygames.top/en/games/Ori_and_the_Blind_Forest.html">https://furrygames.top/en/games/Ori_and_the_Blind_Forest.html</a>
]]></description>
<link>https://furrygames.top/en/games/Ori_and_the_Blind_Forest.html</link>
<guid>https://furrygamesindex.github.io/en/games/Ori_and_the_Blind_Forest.html</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 05:33:54 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Bang×Bang</title>
<description><![CDATA[
	<img width='360' height='168' src='../assets/Bang_Bang/thumbnail.jpg?hc=uquery&t=1675155365' alt='' loading='lazy'><br><br>
	Bang x Bang is a NSFW furry gay story,in this game,you take on the role of a gangster’s son,although you don’t want to be involved in your family business,but a big gang wolf’s advent changed everything……<br><br><br>
	<a href="https://furrygames.top/en/games/Bang_Bang.html">https://furrygames.top/en/games/Bang_Bang.html</a>
]]></description>
<link>https://furrygames.top/en/games/Bang_Bang.html</link>
<guid>https://furrygamesindex.github.io/en/games/Bang_Bang.html</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 08:56:05 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Beast Habitat</title>
<description><![CDATA[
	<img width='360' height='168' src='../assets/Beast_Habitat/thumbnail.jpg?hc=uquery&t=1673952654' alt='' loading='lazy'><br><br>
	你作为偷渡客在充满野兽的「无限兽城」中艰难生活着，随着你记忆不断回归，你终会发现自己所经历的、所遇到的野兽都与你有着千丝万缕的联系。你需要尽可能理顺整个事件，才能知道自己身上所发生的事情究竟为何。<br><br><br>
	<a href="https://furrygames.top/en/games/Beast_Habitat.html">https://furrygames.top/en/games/Beast_Habitat.html</a>
]]></description>
<link>https://furrygames.top/en/games/Beast_Habitat.html</link>
<guid>https://furrygamesindex.github.io/en/games/Beast_Habitat.html</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 10:50:54 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>アルカンシエルの魔獣 / Arc-en-ciel no Majuu (Beasts of Arc-en-ciel)</title>
<description><![CDATA[
	<img width='360' height='168' src='../assets/Arukemo/thumbnail.jpg?hc=uquery&t=1678545989' alt='' loading='lazy'><br><br>
	RPG of beasts seeking rainbows<br>It is a world of beasts and magic.<br>The once glorious land is slowly coming to an end as it is being consumed by mamono and miasma.<br>One day, a lion boy meets a canine boy who has amnesia.<br>He was carrying one of the seven colored keys, which are said to grant the wishes of those who collect them.<br>Thus, the boys&#39; adventure to save the world begins.<br><br>*For players with non-Japanese systems,<br>it may not be possible to decompress and run directly,<br>and you need to use WinRAR or Peazip to adjust the text encoding to Shift-JIS (932) and decompress it to playing normally.<br><br><br>
	<a href="https://furrygames.top/en/games/Arukemo.html">https://furrygames.top/en/games/Arukemo.html</a>
]]></description>
<link>https://furrygames.top/en/games/Arukemo.html</link>
<guid>https://furrygamesindex.github.io/en/games/Arukemo.html</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 07:18:24 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Broken Dreams Correctional Center</title>
<description><![CDATA[
	<img width='360' height='168' src='../assets/Broken_Dreams_Correctional_Center/thumbnail.png?hc=uquery&t=1673448751' alt='' loading='lazy'><br><br>
	BDCC is an erotic text based game about being a prisoner in a space prison with a lot of adult themes.<br><br>It’s obviously a game that involves a lot of bdsm and d/s. The content in this game ranges from vanilla sex to some very dark and sometimes violent stuff. But there are no deaths or guro. It’s also a furry game but you can choose to play as a human or a human-furry hybrid.<br><br>The game&#39;s story will explore many dark topics like legal slavery, forced breeding and others. There is content for both subby and dominant players but obviously switches will get to experience everything.<br><br>This game is influenced a lot by other erotic text rpg games like Trials in the Tainted Space and Lilith&#39;s Throne. The idea of a scifi space prison setting came from a place inside second life called RRDC.<br><br>The game is currently in development and is completely open source.<br><br><br>
	<a href="https://furrygames.top/en/games/Broken_Dreams_Correctional_Center.html">https://furrygames.top/en/games/Broken_Dreams_Correctional_Center.html</a>
]]></description>
<link>https://furrygames.top/en/games/Broken_Dreams_Correctional_Center.html</link>
<guid>https://furrygamesindex.github.io/en/games/Broken_Dreams_Correctional_Center.html</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 14:52:31 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>To Whom I Loved</title>
<description><![CDATA[
	<img width='360' height='168' src='../assets/To_Whom_I_Loved/thumbnail.jpg?hc=uquery&t=1670381857' alt='' loading='lazy'><br><br>
	To Whom I Loved is an 18+ fantasy furry visual novel where you travel as our protagonist (Default name: Asted) to deliver a mysterious letter, only to find yourself stumbling upon a series of unforeseeable events. <br><br><br>
	<a href="https://furrygames.top/en/games/To_Whom_I_Loved.html">https://furrygames.top/en/games/To_Whom_I_Loved.html</a>
]]></description>
<link>https://furrygames.top/en/games/To_Whom_I_Loved.html</link>
<guid>https://furrygamesindex.github.io/en/games/To_Whom_I_Loved.html</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 02:57:37 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Lust Shards</title>
<description><![CDATA[
	<img width='360' height='168' src='../assets/Lust_Shards/thumbnail.jpg?hc=uquery&t=1670380941' alt='' loading='lazy'><br><br>
	This world is filled with Nightfallen, monsters driven by lust and magic, that must be dealt with by Hunters, through whichever means necessary.<br><br>Having been scouted by a prestigious academy for Hunters, you embark on your new life, little did you know, your abilities and looks would catch the eye of a lot of people here, for better or worse. You&#39;ll meet a wide cast of characters with 4 main paths, each with their own quirks and personalities, choose your path and get them to love you!<br><br>This year, it&#39;s just your luck, because the new headmaster is implementing a new start of the year test, to filter out the weak and leave the strong,  who knows why? Maybe you&#39;ll find out.<br><br>If you do not manage to pass the test, then you can say goodbye to your love interests, all that while trying to figure out the secrets of the academy and your new &#39;imaginary&#39; friend.<br><br><br>
	<a href="https://furrygames.top/en/games/Lust_Shards.html">https://furrygames.top/en/games/Lust_Shards.html</a>
]]></description>
<link>https://furrygames.top/en/games/Lust_Shards.html</link>
<guid>https://furrygamesindex.github.io/en/games/Lust_Shards.html</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 02:42:21 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hearthfire</title>
<description><![CDATA[
	<img width='360' height='168' src='../assets/Hearthfire/thumbnail.jpg?hc=uquery&t=1670380257' alt='' loading='lazy'><br><br>
	Taking time off from college and failing grades, Chris decides to get away from everything by getting into his blue sedan and pointing it North. However, violent snow storms ensure that he never makes it to his destination.<br><br>Ending in a violent car crash, Chris finds himself stranded out in the Yukon mountains with no way home. He ends up being dragged from the snow and nursed back to health by an imposing and emotionally closed off polar bear named Tonraq. <br><br>Over time, he&#39;ll learn to crack that frigid exterior and see what&#39;s within as his savior helps him escape the unnatural snowstorms that threaten the polar bear&#39;s home. Along the way, Chris meets others in the small village of Iskut, making unlikely friends as they band together to help the lost otter find his way home.<br><br><br>
	<a href="https://furrygames.top/en/games/Hearthfire.html">https://furrygames.top/en/games/Hearthfire.html</a>
]]></description>
<link>https://furrygames.top/en/games/Hearthfire.html</link>
<guid>https://furrygamesindex.github.io/en/games/Hearthfire.html</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 02:30:57 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>BEYOND THE FAR NORTH</title>
<description><![CDATA[
	<img width='360' height='168' src='../assets/BEYOND_THE_FAR_NORTH/thumbnail.jpg?hc=uquery&t=1669106852' alt='' loading='lazy'><br><br>
	人生の進路に悩んでいたある日、獅子獣人の「ルスタム」は古い手紙を手に入れる。そこには誰も見たことがない言語と地図が記されていた。<br><br>雪で閉ざされた極寒の地には何があるのか……そして、どんな景色が見られるのか……。偶然街へ訪れた犬獣人の自然写真家「ウォルター」と共に、数千kmにも及ぶ旅へ出るのだった──。<br><br><br>
	<a href="https://furrygames.top/en/games/BEYOND_THE_FAR_NORTH.html">https://furrygames.top/en/games/BEYOND_THE_FAR_NORTH.html</a>
]]></description>
<link>https://furrygames.top/en/games/BEYOND_THE_FAR_NORTH.html</link>
<guid>https://furrygamesindex.github.io/en/games/BEYOND_THE_FAR_NORTH.html</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 08:47:32 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Corruption Adventure</title>
<description><![CDATA[
	<img width='360' height='168' src='../assets/Corruption_Adventure/thumbnail.png?hc=uquery&t=1667477450' alt='' loading='lazy'><br><br>
	Corruption Adventure is a NSFW RPG adventure game!<br>You will embark on a journey as the legendary Lord of the Valley of the North Wind, and face the fate of the evil Lord Midnight!<br>In the journey will be filled with all kinds of dangers and tribulations, once you miss, waiting for you will be the punishment of corruption...<br>But as a legendary Lord, even the most dangerous difficulties will not stop you from moving forward, start your journey!<br><br><br>
	<a href="https://furrygames.top/en/games/Corruption_Adventure.html">https://furrygames.top/en/games/Corruption_Adventure.html</a>
]]></description>
<link>https://furrygames.top/en/games/Corruption_Adventure.html</link>
<guid>https://furrygamesindex.github.io/en/games/Corruption_Adventure.html</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 12:10:50 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>One Last Night</title>
<description><![CDATA[
	<img width='360' height='168' src='../assets/One_Last_Night/thumbnail.jpg?hc=uquery&t=1667050556' alt='' loading='lazy'><br><br>
	One Last Night is an 18+ furry visual novel where you play as Dorian, our main character, <br>as he navigates the world around him and the trials he&#39;ll face for the sake of his true love, Marshall. <br><br><br>
	<a href="https://furrygames.top/en/games/One_Last_Night.html">https://furrygames.top/en/games/One_Last_Night.html</a>
]]></description>
<link>https://furrygames.top/en/games/One_Last_Night.html</link>
<guid>https://furrygamesindex.github.io/en/games/One_Last_Night.html</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 13:35:56 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Eclipse City</title>
<description><![CDATA[
	<img width='360' height='168' src='../assets/Eclipse_City/thumbnail.png?hc=uquery&t=1666972759' alt='' loading='lazy'><br><br>
	Eclipse City is a visual novel with action, sci-fi, and romance themes. <br><br>The story follows a human Texas Ranger (Default name: Jack) who ended up in a futuristic world populated by anthropomorphic canines and felines. <br><br>As he tries to maintain his new life in Eclipse City, the Texas Ranger will meet allies and enemies. Will he survive Eclipse City or will Eclipse City consume him?<br><br><br>
	<a href="https://furrygames.top/en/games/Eclipse_City.html">https://furrygames.top/en/games/Eclipse_City.html</a>
]]></description>
<link>https://furrygames.top/en/games/Eclipse_City.html</link>
<guid>https://furrygamesindex.github.io/en/games/Eclipse_City.html</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 15:59:19 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Outland Wanderer</title>
<description><![CDATA[
	<img width='360' height='168' src='../assets/Outland_Wanderer/thumbnail.jpg?hc=uquery&t=1681138163' alt='' loading='lazy'><br><br>
	Player is an outsider stumbling upon the continent of Mokken. In his attempt to travel back to his own Tribe, he bonds and form different relationship with the locals, tackles on unknown forces, and discovers his own destiny.<br>NSFW CG Scenes<br>A focus on delivering different NSFW CG scenes in different scenarios, including the consequences of battles, or progression with a character. Scenes involving more kinks will include a warning beforehand.<br>Quest Log<br>A Branching storyline where every choices, every quests you take on, will have a wider consequences in the future. Quests are given by the characters and have different variety in terms of content.<br>RPG Battle System<br>A Traditional RPG battle system involving the main five stats (STR, INT, TEN, CHA, AGI), a turn-based battle between different kinds of enemies, which requires using different strategies, and abilities,  some foes might have an interest in you after battle...<br>Inventory/Equipment/Crafting/Shop<br>A basic inventory system where items are collected, bought or crafted from scratch, equipment to put on to customise your appearance. Potions and food can be consumed as well.<br>Dungeon Exploration<br>Explore dungeons around the map, solves different puzzles, defeat different monsters and complete unique quests within the dungeon! Dungeon controls involves WASD or Arrow Key movement, or on-screen button.<br><br><br>
	<a href="https://furrygames.top/en/games/Outland_Wanderer.html">https://furrygames.top/en/games/Outland_Wanderer.html</a>
]]></description>
<link>https://furrygames.top/en/games/Outland_Wanderer.html</link>
<guid>https://furrygamesindex.github.io/en/games/Outland_Wanderer.html</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 11:42:48 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Kemono Branch</title>
<description><![CDATA[
	<img width='360' height='168' src='../assets/Kemono_Branch/thumbnail.jpg?hc=uquery&t=1666870129' alt='' loading='lazy'><br><br>
	You and your foster dad went travel and were involved into something strange.<br>The game includes multiple endings and they all based on your choices.<br>However, it&#39;s still a light-hearted game.<br><br><br>
	<a href="https://furrygames.top/en/games/Kemono_Branch.html">https://furrygames.top/en/games/Kemono_Branch.html</a>
]]></description>
<link>https://furrygames.top/en/games/Kemono_Branch.html</link>
<guid>https://furrygamesindex.github.io/en/games/Kemono_Branch.html</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 11:28:49 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>World Flipper</title>
<description><![CDATA[
	<img width='360' height='168' src='../assets/World_Flipper/thumbnail.jpg?hc=uquery&t=1666775152' alt='' loading='lazy'><br><br>
	Don&#39;t miss out on this EPIC pinball adventure!<br><br>◆ PINBALL MEETS ACTION RPG!<br>Everything you love about pinball packed into an action RPG! Experience pinball like you never have before!<br><br>◆ FAST-PACED COMBAT!<br>Ready, aim, fire! Time your attacks right and crush your foes before they know what hit &#39;em. Activate skills to maximize damage!<br><br>◆ EXPLORE FANTASY WORLDS!<br>Travel across several worlds, each with its own friends to meet and mysteries to unravel!<br><br>◆ STRATEGIZE AND BUILD YOUR TEAM!<br>In World Flipper, units can pair up and combine their abilities.<br>Find the perfect duo, and unlock game-breaking combo skills.<br><br>◆ TAKE ON CO-OP BOSS BATTLES!<br>Team up with friends, link together skill chains, and bring down nightmarish foes!<br><br>◆ DIVE INTO THE STORY BEHIND EACH CHARACTER!<br>Every character is beautifully illustrated, with episodic story arcs to unlock!<br><br>◆ NOSTALGIC PIXEL ART!<br>Watch the story unfold in adorable pixel animation. It&#39;s a whole epic in your pocket.<br><br><br>
	<a href="https://furrygames.top/en/games/World_Flipper.html">https://furrygames.top/en/games/World_Flipper.html</a>
]]></description>
<link>https://furrygames.top/en/games/World_Flipper.html</link>
<guid>https://furrygamesindex.github.io/en/games/World_Flipper.html</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 09:05:52 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Night Sky</title>
<description><![CDATA[
	<img width='360' height='168' src='../assets/Night_Sky/thumbnail.jpg?hc=uquery&t=1665607375' alt='' loading='lazy'><br><br>
	A boy with weird dreams, wondering why it always happens every night. No family except his big brother though they are both unrelated by blood. One day, the world had a pandemic where everyone was affected. Due to that, school interruption happened. The boy now struggles with his mysterious dreams, brother problems, new friends and best friends, and the pandemic.<br><br>The Night Sky is a visual novel about a human boy who was born in a world of furry. Follow the adventure of the main protagonist to a place where various consequences will happen by deciding the choices to be made<br><br><br>
	<a href="https://furrygames.top/en/games/Night_Sky.html">https://furrygames.top/en/games/Night_Sky.html</a>
]]></description>
<link>https://furrygames.top/en/games/Night_Sky.html</link>
<guid>https://furrygamesindex.github.io/en/games/Night_Sky.html</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 20:42:55 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Sylving</title>
<description><![CDATA[
	<img width='360' height='168' src='../assets/Sylving/thumbnail.jpg?hc=uquery&t=1665607375' alt='' loading='lazy'><br><br>
	Sylving is a furry visual novel with romance, adventure, drama, action and comedy. Travel to another world where different anthropomorphic people live, where a long history of conflict has been going between the Dyr, Udyr and Eldor races for centuries, but not without reasons. You&#39;ll meet many different characters and learn more about this world, but not everyone is what they seem to be at first glance. <br><br><br>
	<a href="https://furrygames.top/en/games/Sylving.html">https://furrygames.top/en/games/Sylving.html</a>
]]></description>
<link>https://furrygames.top/en/games/Sylving.html</link>
<guid>https://furrygamesindex.github.io/en/games/Sylving.html</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 20:42:55 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Wild Lips</title>
<description><![CDATA[
	<img width='360' height='168' src='../assets/Wild_Lips/thumbnail.jpg?hc=uquery&t=1665607375' alt='' loading='lazy'><br><br>
	A tiger saves you from being killed by a dark and strange figure. You want to meet him, but all he&#39;s trying to do is push you away. During your adventure to meet your savior, you will meet several boys who will catch your eye and change your life.<br><br>Which path will you choose? And what does the future hold for you?<br><br><br>
	<a href="https://furrygames.top/en/games/Wild_Lips.html">https://furrygames.top/en/games/Wild_Lips.html</a>
]]></description>
<link>https://furrygames.top/en/games/Wild_Lips.html</link>
<guid>https://furrygamesindex.github.io/en/games/Wild_Lips.html</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 20:42:55 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Deers and Deckards</title>
<description><![CDATA[
	<img width='360' height='168' src='../assets/Deers_and_Deckards/thumbnail.jpg?hc=uquery&t=1665455018' alt='' loading='lazy'><br><br>
	You goes to visit your best friend for a fun weekend of games. There you also get to meet his dad, making the stay more eventful then expected...<br><br><br>
	<a href="https://furrygames.top/en/games/Deers_and_Deckards.html">https://furrygames.top/en/games/Deers_and_Deckards.html</a>
]]></description>
<link>https://furrygames.top/en/games/Deers_and_Deckards.html</link>
<guid>https://furrygamesindex.github.io/en/games/Deers_and_Deckards.html</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 17:04:17 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Heartbeat Faraway</title>
<description><![CDATA[
	<img width='360' height='168' src='../assets/Heartbeat_Faraway/thumbnail.jpg?hc=uquery&t=1664937862' alt='' loading='lazy'><br><br>
	Heartbeat Faraway融合了节奏与文字冒险玩法，是一款关于选择与救赎的游戏。<br><br>你将扮演一名自杀热线的接线员，面对形形色色的患者，他们或因为职场的压力产生焦虑，或因为生活的变故逐渐失控，你要做的，就是通过选择合适的对话解开他们的心结，让他们完成心灵的救赎，与自己和解。<br><br><br>
	<a href="https://furrygames.top/en/games/Heartbeat_Faraway.html">https://furrygames.top/en/games/Heartbeat_Faraway.html</a>
]]></description>
<link>https://furrygames.top/en/games/Heartbeat_Faraway.html</link>
<guid>https://furrygamesindex.github.io/en/games/Heartbeat_Faraway.html</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 02:44:22 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Furry University AfterRebirth</title>
<description><![CDATA[
	<img width='360' height='168' src='../assets/Furry_University_Rebirth/thumbnail.jpg?hc=uquery&t=1674225786' alt='' loading='lazy'><br><br>
	《兽人大学：启示录》的坏结局后发生的故事。玩家，也就是你，将扮演性取向为男性的新生陈川来到兽都上学。<br><br>在游戏的过程中，你将遇到你的室友刘川，你的宿管阿卢，你对门的邻居李军，与你专业课相同的白锋，楼底旧猫巷的代班老板孙熊，还有你的足球老师亚格斯。<br><br>无论如何，你将自己决定如何与他们相处。你可以选择成为一名乖乖学生念完大学，或者与与某位你中意的兽人产生纯情关系。当然，你也能臣服于你的肉体，成为名副其实的“烂裤裆”，与多位兽人发生肉体关系。<br><br><br>
	<a href="https://furrygames.top/en/games/Furry_University_Rebirth.html">https://furrygames.top/en/games/Furry_University_Rebirth.html</a>
]]></description>
<link>https://furrygames.top/en/games/Furry_University_Rebirth.html</link>
<guid>https://furrygamesindex.github.io/en/games/Furry_University_Rebirth.html</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 01:28:03 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>My Time At Etheria</title>
<description><![CDATA[
	<img width='360' height='168' src='../assets/My_Time_At_Etheria/thumbnail.png?hc=uquery&t=1664610184' alt='' loading='lazy'><br><br>
	After waking up from a bizarre dream, you find yourself lost in the middle of the woods. Unfamiliar with your surrounding, you decided to make your way out of the forest...<br><br><br>
	<a href="https://furrygames.top/en/games/My_Time_At_Etheria.html">https://furrygames.top/en/games/My_Time_At_Etheria.html</a>
]]></description>
<link>https://furrygames.top/en/games/My_Time_At_Etheria.html</link>
<guid>https://furrygamesindex.github.io/en/games/My_Time_At_Etheria.html</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 07:43:04 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>My Pirate Husbandos</title>
<description><![CDATA[
	<img width='360' height='168' src='../assets/My_Pirate_Husbandos/thumbnail.jpg?hc=uquery&t=1664251585' alt='' loading='lazy'><br><br>
	Having nearly drowned at sea you find yourself an outsider among the handsome pirate crew who rescued you. They sail by day, do depraved things at night, and you can&#39;t keep your mind from thinking about them.<br><br>Set sail into the sexy and dangerous story of My Pirate Husbandos. <br><br><br>
	<a href="https://furrygames.top/en/games/My_Pirate_Husbandos.html">https://furrygames.top/en/games/My_Pirate_Husbandos.html</a>
]]></description>
<link>https://furrygames.top/en/games/My_Pirate_Husbandos.html</link>
<guid>https://furrygamesindex.github.io/en/games/My_Pirate_Husbandos.html</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 04:06:25 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Stray</title>
<description><![CDATA[
	<img width='360' height='168' src='../assets/Stray/thumbnail.jpg?hc=uquery&t=1664193822' alt='' loading='lazy'><br><br>
	About This Game<br>Lost, alone and separated from family, a stray cat must untangle an ancient mystery to escape a long-forgotten city.<br>Stray is a third-person cat adventure game set amidst the detailed, neon-lit alleys of a decaying cybercity and the murky environments of its seedy underbelly. Roam surroundings high and low, defend against unforeseen threats and solve the mysteries of this unwelcoming place inhabited by curious droids and dangerous creatures.<br>See the world through the eyes of a cat and interact with the environment in playful ways. Be stealthy, nimble, silly, and sometimes as annoying as possible with the strange inhabitants of this mysterious world.<br>Along the way, the cat befriends a small flying drone, known only as B-12. With the help of this newfound companion, the duo must find a way out.<br>Stray is developed by BlueTwelve Studio, a small team from the south of France mostly made up of cats and a handful of humans.<br><br><br>
	<a href="https://furrygames.top/en/games/Stray.html">https://furrygames.top/en/games/Stray.html</a>
]]></description>
<link>https://furrygames.top/en/games/Stray.html</link>
<guid>https://furrygamesindex.github.io/en/games/Stray.html</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 12:03:42 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Spirit: Summoners of Áine-Chlair</title>
<description><![CDATA[
	<img width='360' height='168' src='../assets/Spirit_Summoners_of_Aine_Chlair/thumbnail.png?hc=uquery&t=1664109599' alt='' loading='lazy'><br><br>
	Daigo &#34;Damian&#34; Minazuki (水無月 大悟 Minazuki Daigo) is a 23-year-old wolf who is cheerful, optimistic, and simple to the point of being ditzy—this, however, conceals his tragic past. After leaving his hometown, Rougetsu Village, Damian came to Asou City, working as a wage earner in Happy Street Mall. He hopes that he might spend his entire life surrounded by smiles and laughter, but wouldn&#39;t care if people didn&#39;t miss him if he was gone. However, as rumors start to spread of people in Asou City starting to go missing one after another,  Damian encounters a kobold-like creature. From that moment on, his life would never be the same again...<br><br><br>
	<a href="https://furrygames.top/en/games/Spirit_Summoners_of_Aine_Chlair.html">https://furrygames.top/en/games/Spirit_Summoners_of_Aine_Chlair.html</a>
]]></description>
<link>https://furrygames.top/en/games/Spirit_Summoners_of_Aine_Chlair.html</link>
<guid>https://furrygamesindex.github.io/en/games/Spirit_Summoners_of_Aine_Chlair.html</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 25 Sep 2022 12:39:59 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Gomamon Trainer</title>
<description><![CDATA[
	<img width='360' height='168' src='../assets/Gomamon_Trainer/thumbnail.jpg?hc=uquery&t=1663340039' alt='' loading='lazy'><br><br>
	The world you find yourself in is not the digital world you know however, but a strange In-Between-World and you have to find your way out with Gomamon by your side. Talk, Molest and Fuck the little digimon however you please as you advance further to escape with him by your side.<br><br>You can either be nice or mean to him, depending if you want him to be your Lover Slut or Slave Slut. As this is an unfinished game, this feature has no effect as of yet.<br><br>Gomamon Trainer is a work-in-progress visual novel digimon smut game which pushes you into a strange digital world, trapped with a cute male Gomamon. The very same Gomamon from Digimon Adventure.<br><br>This is a simple enough game. You press buttons to advance the game, talk and molest Gomamon. It is heavily inspired by My Very Own Lith and I recommend you check it out in case it is unknown to you.<br><br>This is an unfinished game and will still need many resources to be completed.<br><br><br>
	<a href="https://furrygames.top/en/games/Gomamon_Trainer.html">https://furrygames.top/en/games/Gomamon_Trainer.html</a>
]]></description>
<link>https://furrygames.top/en/games/Gomamon_Trainer.html</link>
<guid>https://furrygamesindex.github.io/en/games/Gomamon_Trainer.html</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 14:53:59 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Cult of the Lamb</title>
<description><![CDATA[
	<img width='360' height='168' src='../assets/Cult_of_the_Lamb/thumbnail.jpg?hc=uquery&t=1661526478' alt='' loading='lazy'><br><br>
	Cult of the Lamb casts players in the role of a possessed lamb saved from annihilation by an ominous stranger, and must repay their debt by building a loyal following in his name. Start your own cult in a land of false prophets, venturing out into diverse and mysterious regions to build a loyal community of woodland Followers and spread your Word to become the one true cult.<br>BUILD YOUR FLOCK<br>Collect and use resources to build new structures, perform dark rituals to appease the gods, and give sermons to reinforce the faith of your flock.<br>DESTROY THE NON-BELIEVERS<br>Explore a sprawling, randomly generated world, fight off hordes of enemies and defeat rival cult leaders in order to absorb their power and assert your cult&#39;s dominance.<br>SPREAD YOUR WORD<br>Train your flock and embark on a quest to explore and discover the secrets of four mysterious regions. Cleanse the non-believers, spread enlightenment, and perform mystical rituals on the journey to become the mighty lamb god.<br><br><br>
	<a href="https://furrygames.top/en/games/Cult_of_the_Lamb.html">https://furrygames.top/en/games/Cult_of_the_Lamb.html</a>
]]></description>
<link>https://furrygames.top/en/games/Cult_of_the_Lamb.html</link>
<guid>https://furrygamesindex.github.io/en/games/Cult_of_the_Lamb.html</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2022 15:07:58 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>